# Robert Ferrer

# **Summary**

I have always worked with customer service, with more than 20 years of experience, being Magazine Luiza 8 years and Santander 9 years. I am an observer, analyst and I have an entrepreneurial vision, I have the ability to work as a team, as a collaborator I always try to be active in projects to achieve the desired success, seeking to leverage sales with excellence in customer service.

## **Experience**

# **Business and Services Manager**

Santander Bank, Jau, SP Brazil

Customer service, account opening, sale of financial services, insurance, telephone and visits, cashier.

From 2013-08 to 2022-04

#### Salesman

Magazine Luiza, Jau, SP Brazil

I worked 5 years as a salesperson in all sectors and later as a cashier for 3 years.

From 2003-10 to 2011-09

#### Education

# **Systems Developer**

ETEC - Etec Joaquim Ferreira do Amaral From 2021-07 to 2022-12

**MBA** in Administration and Finance UNINTER Centro Universitário Internacional From 2014-06 to 2015-12

**Specialization** in Production Engineering UNINTER Centro Universitário Internacional From 2013-02 to 2014-06

**Bachelor** in Business Administration Faculdades Integradas de Jaú From 2007-02 to 2010-12

# Certification and Licenses B1 IELTS

Intermediary English in 2021-06

#### CPA-10

ANBIMA Brazilian Association of Financial and Capital Markets Entities
From 2014-01 to 2023-12

#### **Contacts**

# **Phone number** +55 14 99860-8309

# Address

Jaú, SP - Brazil

### **Nationality**

Brazilian

#### E-mail:

ferrerrobert@outlook.com

#### Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/RobertFerrer7

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/RobertFe rrer7